[Music]
so so when Putin came late to the lunch
meeting they had should Obama have a put
his dick on the table at
lunch come on Larry that's
disgusting sorry you starting your own
University won't work no no no my
graduates won't work okay uh no no
swear listen I'm I'm I'm literally not
teaching them any marketable at all it's
amazing but I have to say what I am
teaching them is how to link their
checking accounts for direct deposit to
my es Corp which is located in
Switzerland it is simple trumponomics
okay what should Obama do right now
situation I mean personally if I was
Obama I'd be like this is what I'm going
to do it
uh I we have we've made a commitment to
our friends uh uh
uh what and then you just forget about
it everything's over yeah it's all over
the whole conflict is gone hey America
Larry Wilmore here if you like the
nightly show on Comedy Central like us
on Facebook too just don't poke me I do
not like being poked you can Candy Crush
me